Hand me that flashlight."
(Sheldon:)Those were the last words
(Sheldon:)he ever spoke to us.
(Leonard:)I don't think you need
(Leonard:)to worry about death by badgers
being hereditary.
(Sheldon:)Not true.
(Sheldon:)The fight or flight instinct
is coded genetically.
(Sheldon:)Instead of fleeing, he chose
to fight barehanded
(Sheldon:)against a brawny member
of the weasel family.
(Sheldon:)Who's to say that I don't share
that flawed DNA?
(Leonard:)You can always get a badger
and find out.
(Sheldon:)But seriously,
(Sheldon:)even if I disregard
the Uncle Carl factor,
(Sheldon:)at best I have 60 years left.
(Leonard:)That long, huh?
(Sheldon:)60 only takes me to here.
(Sheldon:)I need to get to here.
(Leonard:)What's there?
(Sheldon:)The earliest estimate
of the singularity,
(Sheldon:)when man will be able
to transfer his consciousness
(Sheldon:)into machines
and achieve immortality.
(Leonard:)So, you're upset
about missing out
(Leonard:)on becoming some sort of
freakish self-aware robot?